(Leonard:)Sheldon, there are a million
great vacations you could take.
(Leonard:)What about Hawaii?
Hawaii is a former Ieper colony
on top of an active volcano...
(Sheldon:)...where the disappointing ending
to Lost was filmed.
(Sheldon:)Mahalo for nothing, Hawaii.
(Howard:)How about Florida?
They got Cape Canaveral,
they got Disney.
They got my Aunt lda and the world's
Iargest collection of diabetic candy.
And plus, if you get sweaty enough...
(Howard:)...her plastic-covered furniture
is Iike a flume ride.
(Sheldon:)My family took a trip to Florida
when I was a child.
(Sheldon:)A seagull stole a hot dog from me
on the beach.
(Sheldon:)I got the message.
(Raj:)If I had a week off...
(Raj:)...I'd go back to the Two Bunch Palms
Resort and Spa in the desert.
(Raj:)I tell you, an hour on the massage table
with Trevor...
(Raj:)...and you'll feel like you were born
without bones.
(Howard:)I don't think I could ever let a guy
give me a massage.